Guide to the Committee on Admissions Records, 1946-1988 UA 179
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Committee on Admissions Records
1946-1988
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University. Admissions Committee
UA 179
1 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
Records pertaining to the Rice University Admissions Committee between 1946 and 1988. Includes admission forms, minutes, memos, reports, and correspondence.
Historical Note
The Admission Committee consists of faculty and students who participate in the admissions process at Rice University, as well as regularly evaluate the university's recruitment and admisison methods.
Scope and Contents
Contains minutes, memoranda, reports, and correspondence of the Admission Committees from 1946-1988 from the papers of Presidents William V. Houston, Kenneth Pitzer, Norman Hackerman, and George Rupp.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Restrictions on Access
Access to this material requires permission from the Office of the President - please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for assistance.
Accruals
No future additions are expected for this material.
Provenance
President's papers (Pitzer, Hackerman, Rupp); Provost's papers; Vice President for Adminstration papers
Related Materials
Office of the President records and Office of Admissions records, 1985-2005
Index Terms
Subjects
Admissions Committee; Universities and colleges
Document Types
memorandums; minutes (administrative records); reports; corrrespondence
Places
Rice University
Subjects (Persons)
Rupp, George; Hackerman, Norman; Pitzer, Kenneth S. (Kenneth Sanborn); Houston, W. V. (William Vermillion)
- Committee on Admissions Records, 69799
  - Admission Forms, 69815 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, Memoranda, Reports, Correspondence, 1946-1948; 69814 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, Memoranda, Reports, etc., 1947-1958/59; 69813 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1959/60-1961/62; 69812 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1962/63-1964/65; 69811 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1965/66-1967/68; 69810 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1968/69-1969/70; 69809 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1970/71-1971/72; 69808 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1972/73-1973/74; 69807 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1974/75-1975/76; 69806 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1976/77-1977/78; 69805 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1978/79-1979/80; 69804 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1980/81-1984/85; 69803 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, Correspondence, 1985-86; 69802 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1986-87; 69801 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, Memos, Reports, etc., 1987-88; 69800 (Box 2, Folder 2)